navioo.com 2013-05-19

# 

****

This is the web site of **EPSYLONSYS.inc**.  
We can be reached clicking on [ EPSYLONSYS.inc ](http://www.epsilonsys.com/web/contact.php)

**EPSYLONSYS.inc** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: all EPSYLONSYS.inc sites are operated by **EPSYLONSYS.inc** , located in Montreal -Brossard, CANADA.

**EPSYLONSYS.inc** is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. **EPSYLONSYS.inc** collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

Your IP address is used only when you become a member as a backup identification tool for polls and other member services or as identification tool when you post messages in our forums.  
Our site may use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and the content contained is not distributed to third parties.

This site contains links to other sites. EPSYLONSYS.inc is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our online surveys may ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). The customer's contact information is only used to contact the visitor when necessary. We do not share this information with third parties.

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the [NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.

**Comments**  
EPSYLONSYS.inc makes use of message boards (known as Comments), available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Communication**  
Registered users should not expect any unsolicited or promotional email from EPSYLONSYS.inc.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Public Forums**  
Our site makes forums and message boards, available free to users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Our servers have strict security in place to prevent an intruder from retrieving personal information about our users. Staff checks server access daily to ensure the above holds true.

**Children's Guidelines**  
This site gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact **EPSYLONSYS.inc**.
